Do the D-A-S-D-E 1-2-3-4, FIGHT!
Stick to the B-E-E-D-A-Z Get ready to ignite
You are such a B-Y-E Catching all the lights
Just easy, or ABC that's how you make it right
Do the D-A-S-D-E 1-2-3-4, FIGHT!
Stick to the B-E-E-A-Z Get ready to ignite
You are such a B-Y-E Catching all the lights
Just easy, or ABC that's how you make it right
Do the D-A-S-D-E Stick to the B-E-E-A-Z
Just easy, or ABC Do the dance, do the dance
The way you move is a mystery
Do the dance You always have a redicule in me
Do the dance The way you move is a mystery
Do the D-A-S-D-E 1-2-3-4, FIGHT!
Stick to the B-E-E-A-Z Get ready to ignite
You are such a B-Y-E Catching all the lights
Just easy, or ABC that's how you make it right
Do the dance The way you move is a mystery
Do the dance You always have a redicule in me
Do the dance
Do the D-A-S-D-E Do the dance, do the dance
Stick to the B-E-E-A-Z Do the dance, do the dance
You are such a B-Y-E Do the dance, do the dance
Just easy, or ABC Do the dance, do the dance
Under the spotlights Neither black nor white
It doesn't matter Do the dance, do the dance
As tall as you might Working day and night
Whatever happens Do the dance, do the dance
Under the spotlights Neither black nor white
It doesn't matter Do the dance, do the dance
As tall as you might Working day and night
Whatever happens Do the dance, do the dance
The way you move is a mystery Do the dance
You always have a redicule in me
The way you move is a mystery